THOMAS "ANDY" WAGER

7120 Brittany Drive, Fort Collins, CO | 605.769.1363 | tawager@gmail.com

Web Development & Marketing

Work Hard, Love Life

Personal Website — www.tawager.com

Creative Web Developer with demonstrated expertise in communications, marketing, and programming. Proven success combining a scientific/analytic approach with a keen eye for design to create exceptional user experiences. Known for being an incredibly fast learner and for having a relentless commitment to surpassing expectations.

Areas of Expertise:

- ✓ HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- ✓ UI/UX
- ✓ Content Creation / Technical Writing
- ✓ Marketing Collateral Development

- ✓ Social Media Campaigns / SEO
- ✓ Adobe C.S.
- ✓ Photo / Video Editing
- ✓ Mac/PC Operating Systems

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

Andie's List (www.AndiesList.org)

• Co-founder of Andies's List, a site that reviews and evaluates local non-profit organizations.

Cu29 Creations (www.Cu29Creations.com) - coming soon

Site includes extensive photo gallery components with e-commerce/retail plug-in.

To-Do and Personal Dashboard Web App (url TBD)

Task Management tool that allows users to create lists, set priorities, and link to photos.

SELECT MARKETING ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Social Media Campaigns

• Created and executed 10 plus social media campaigns utilizing wide variety of social media platforms to successfully increase interest/awareness, promote events and drive revenue.

Graphic Design and Layout

• Highly adept at the using the Adobe C.S. to design posters, brochures and other marketing materials in order to engage and educate target audiences about events and programs.

Content Creation, Writing and Editing

- Professional writer and editor with experience providing fresh copy and editing content for magazines, newspapers, and websites; authored weekly newspaper column.
- Final editor of studio screenplay, "Fatherland," and webisode series, "And, We're Back."

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Marketing Assistant – The Fine Art & Frame Company 01/2013 – 07/2013 Fort Collins, Colorado

Intern/Social Media Director/Columnist/Editor – BizNOW Magazine 01/2012 – 07/2014 Sioux Falls, South Dakota

Reporter/Columnist – Potter County News 05/2010 – 09/2010 Gettysburg, South Dakota

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Bachelor of Science – Mass Communication South Dakota State University – Brookings, South Dakota

Web Development Certificate – WebLab, Web Development Boot Camp Front Range Community College – Boulder, Colorado